<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://www.cafeauchain.com/blog/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://www.cafeauchain.com/blog/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-02T11:06:57-04:00</updated><id>https://www.cafeauchain.com/blog/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Cafe au Chain</title><subtitle>Cafe au Chain is a blockchain-backed inventory management platform for the specialty coffee industry. Our mission is to provide tools for coffee roasters, producers and farmers, and traders that make transparency around  economic and environmental sustainability easier.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Proof of Perk Launches</title><link href="https://www.cafeauchain.com/blog/2019/03/29/proof-of-perk-launch.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Proof of Perk Launches" /><published>2019-03-29T10:45:13-04:00</published><updated>2019-03-29T10:45:13-04:00</updated><id>https://www.cafeauchain.com/blog/2019/03/29/proof-of-perk-launch</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://www.cafeauchain.com/blog/2019/03/29/proof-of-perk-launch.html">&lt;p&gt;It's finally here!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nearly a year since we decided to take Cafe au Chain from an exploratory idea to a series of experiments designed to grow into a business, we’ve launched the culmination of the first set of experiments: Proof of Perk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;img class=&quot;img-fluid&quot; src=&quot;/blog/img/posts/pop-screenshot-Mar-19.jpg&quot;&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;caption text-muted&quot;&gt;Integrated roasting production and inventory management backed by blockchain.&lt;/span&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Proof of Perk (named after the economic measure concept &lt;a href='https://www.wikiwand.com/en/Proof-of-work_system'&gt;proof of work&lt;/a&gt;) is designed to be an integrated inventory management platform and wholesale portal. Roasters can now track how much green coffee they have remaining in a contract, how much they have on hand, and how much they’ve roasted of any particular contract in any given time period. That data is automatically updated as wholesale orders from approved customers come in, filling your roast queue and calculating how much of any particular coffee and roast profile is needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;section-heading&quot;&gt;Just a Piece of the Puzzle&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As part of our platform’s mission, each action that’s taken on a particular pound of coffee, from delivery to the roaster, through roasting and fulfillment of orders, is being tracked as a transaction on the Cafe au Chain back end. Proof of Perk is just one interface into the full, transparent supply chain that’s our mission to support and build.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There have been pivots, reassessments, and periods of reflection, but eventually, you just have to put something out there and see how people respond. We’re excited to get you enrolled on Proof of Perk, and to get your feedback on how we can improve the platform to better serve you. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;subheading&quot;&gt;Side note: if you’re interested in getting first access to new features and helping us improve our platform, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:info@cafeauchain.com?subject=Inquiry about First Crack Beta Program&quot;&gt;send us a message&lt;/a&gt; about joining the First Crack Beta Program.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It's finally here!</summary></entry></feed>